Come on!
(Leonard:)Yeah, Penny might be onto something.
-To the planetarium!
-Let's go!
-To the tar pits!
There's a Nell Diamond
concert next month!
Let's go!
(Penny:)Three bags, no one's opened 'em.
Ware the first ones here!
(Sheldon:)-It's dirty laundry. You're up.
-Why me?
(Sheldon:)Because you've been training
for this your whole life.
(Sheldon:)You live in a pile of dirty laundry.
(Bernadette:)They're here first.
This is because
(Bernadette:)you made me slow down
for that blind guy.
(Penny:)-Okay, the clue must be in the bag.
-The clue must be in the bag.
(Penny:)-It's just a bunch of pants.
-It's just a bunch of pants.
(Penny:)You know, I'm surprised
you want to copy my answers
(Penny:)since I'm not even smart
enough to be on your team.
(Leonard:)Well, why would you want
to be on someone's team
(Leonard:)who you like to call a-- I can't
even say it in front of Sheldon.